## **Dmitrii Liulekin**

Fronend developer

Georgia, Tbilisi +995 5511 01 972 Iyulekin.dima@gmail.com @dimalyulekin (Telegram)

## **About**

Frontend developer with almost 4 years of experience designing and building responsive web platforms and SPAs. Proficient with CSS, ReactJS(Typescript), NextJs, a lot of knowledges of UX/UI and users psychology.

So, being experienced in 3D animation, I'm looking for the great animated project in 2d or 3d context(WebGL) to contribute my skills and improve myself as well.

## **Experience**

2022 - Present

**LLC TechWings** 

Frontend developer

Built dynamic business Instagram (web-app-NextJS, mobile-app-ReactNative&Reanimated2, admin panel-React). Used WebAnimation API for animations, that can be paused, resumed, played forwards and backwards, accelerated, etc. Created story npm-package that is used by web-app, admin panel and mobile-app. Made up admin stories constructor (admin can configure, create and edit any story. All stories have real-time preview with animations and separated steps). Also, every story can be recorded on Backend side (using Puppeteer, FFmpeg and some own libraries) and exported as GIF, MP4 or ZIP.

2019 - 2022

LLC STL

Frontend developer

Implemented online-payments, online-scoring, rating calculation, auto-seed for different tournament types. Made up role-separation. Built Judges learning platform with exams. Created online game for young players using canvas. Helped to switch project from PhP on SSR(Next) and React(Typescript).

## **Education**

2008 - 2012

Web design Lyceum of IT 2012 - 2016

**Sport Specialist** RSUPE

2016 - 2018

Master of Sociology RSUPE 2018 - 2020

Elite Sport RSUPE

2017 - 2019

**3D Generalist** CGTarian School

2018 - 2019

Frontend Dev LLC Yandex 2021 - 2021

**UX/UI Designer** LLC Yandex 2021 - 2022

Middle Frontend Dev LLC Yandex